{
    "$schema": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/revisit-studies/study/v2.2.0/src/parser/StudyConfigSchema.json",
    "studyMetadata": {
        "title": "RRNL MSZ Study",
        "version": "pilot",
        "authors": [
            "Morgan Vasiliou, Skylar Lin, ZoÃ« Fisk"
        ],
        "date": "2026-02-16",
        "description": "A simple questionnaire study",
        "organizations": [
            "WPI"
        ]
    },
    "uiConfig": {
        "contactEmail": "gr-datavis-26@wpi.edu",
        "helpTextPath": "rrnl/assets/help.md",
        "logoPath": "revisitAssets/revisitLogoSquare.svg",
        "withProgressBar": true,
        "autoDownloadStudy": false,
        "withSidebar": true
    },
    "components": {
        "introduction": {
            "type": "markdown",
            "path": "rrnl/assets/introduction.md",
            "response": [],
            "meta": {
                "taskId": "introduction",
                "trackTime": true
            }
        },
        "participant-stats": {
            "type": "questionnaire",
            "response": [
                {
                    "id": "q1-age",
                    "prompt": "What is your age group?",
                    "required": true,
                    "location": "aboveStimulus",
                    "type": "dropdown",
                    "placeholder": "Please enter your age group",
                    "options": ["18-40", "40-60"]
                }
            ],
            "meta": {
                "taskId": "participant-stats",
                "trackTime": true
            }
        },
        "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/A_bloodGlucose_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 2.3,
                        "acceptableLow": 2.0,
                        "acceptableHigh": 2.6
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 12.2,
                        "acceptableLow": 11.9,
                        "acceptableHigh": 12.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "A_bloodGlucose_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/A_bloodGlucose_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 5.2,
                        "acceptableLow": 4.9,
                        "acceptableHigh": 5.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 6.3,
                        "acceptableLow": 6.0,
                        "acceptableHigh": 6.6
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "A_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "A_bloodPressure_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/A_bloodPressure_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 147,
                        "acceptableLow": 144,
                        "acceptableHigh": 150
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 105,
                        "acceptableLow": 102,
                        "acceptableHigh": 108
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "A_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "A_bloodPressure_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/A_bloodPressure_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 137,
                        "acceptableLow": 134,
                        "acceptableHigh": 140
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 75.5,
                        "acceptableLow": 72.5,
                        "acceptableHigh": 78.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "A_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "A_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/B_bloodGlucose_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 10,
                        "acceptableLow": 9.7,
                        "acceptableHigh": 10.3
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 2.5,
                        "acceptableLow": 2.2,
                        "acceptableHigh": 2.8
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "B_bloodGlucose_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/B_bloodGlucose_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "B_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "B_bloodPressure_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/B_bloodPressure_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 63
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 94
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "B_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "B_bloodPressure_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/B_bloodPressure_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "B_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "B_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/C_bloodGlucose_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 1.1,
                        "acceptableLow": 0.8,
                        "acceptableHigh": 1.4
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 3.2,
                        "acceptableLow": 2.9,
                        "acceptableHigh": 3.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "C_bloodGlucose_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/C_bloodGlucose_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 5.6,
                        "acceptableLow": 5.3,
                        "acceptableHigh": 5.9
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 7.2,
                        "acceptableLow": 6.9,
                        "acceptableHigh": 7.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "C_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "C_bloodPressure_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/C_bloodPressure_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 145,
                        "acceptableLow": 142,
                        "acceptableHigh": 148
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 107,
                        "acceptableLow": 104,
                        "acceptableHigh": 110
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "C_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "C_bloodPressure_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/C_bloodPressure_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 115,
                        "acceptableLow": 112,
                        "acceptableHigh": 118
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 77,
                        "acceptableLow": 74,
                        "acceptableHigh": 80
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "C_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "C_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/D_bloodGlucose_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 7.8,
                        "acceptableLow": 7.5,
                        "acceptableHigh": 8.1
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 1319,
                        "acceptableLow": 1316,
                        "acceptableHigh": 1322
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "D_bloodGlucose_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/D_bloodGlucose_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the fasting blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the two hours postprandial blood glucose value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is fasting blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is two hours postprandial blood glucose normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_value",
                        "answer": 5.6,
                        "acceptableLow": 5.3,
                        "acceptableHigh": 5.9
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_value",
                        "answer": 9.2,
                        "acceptableLow": 8.9,
                        "acceptableHigh": 9.5
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_fasting_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodGlucose_normal_postprandial_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "D_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "D_bloodPressure_abnormal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/D_bloodPressure_abnormal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 148,
                        "acceptableLow": 145,
                        "acceptableHigh": 151
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 101,
                        "acceptableLow": 98,
                        "acceptableHigh": 104
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "D_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "D_bloodPressure_normal": {
                "type": "website",
                "path": "rrnl/assets/D_bloodPressure_normal.html",
                "response": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the systolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "prompt": "What is the diastolic value?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "numerical",
                        "placeholder": "Enter numerical value"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is systolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "prompt": "Is diastolic normal?",
                        "required": true,
                        "location": "belowStimulus",
                        "type": "dropdown",
                        "options": ["Yes", "No"]
                    }
                ],
                "correctAnswer": [
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_value",
                        "answer": 138,
                        "acceptableLow": 135,
                        "acceptableHigh": 141
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_value",
                        "answer": 87,
                        "acceptableLow": 84,
                        "acceptableHigh": 90
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_systolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "id": "D_bloodPressure_normal_diastolic_normal",
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    }
                ],
                "instructionLocation": "aboveStimulus",
                "allowFailedTraining": true,
                "meta": {
                    "taskId": "D_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "trackTime": true
                }
        },
        "break-component": {
            "type": "website",
            "path": "rrnl/assets/break-timer.html",
            "response": [],
            "meta": {
                "taskId": "break-component",
                "trackTime": true
            }
        },
        "study-results": {
            "type": "website",
            "path": "rrnl/assets/results.html",
            "response": [],
            "meta": {
                "taskId": "study-results",
                "trackTime": true
            }
        }
    },
    "sequence": {
        "order": "fixed",
        "components": [
            "introduction",
            "participant-stats",
            {
                "order": "random",
                "components": [
                    "A_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "A_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "B_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "B_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "C_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "C_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "D_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "D_bloodPressure_abnormal"
                ]
            },
            "break-component",
            {
                "order": "random",
                "components": [
                    "A_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "A_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "B_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "B_bloodPressure_normal",
                    "C_bloodGlucose_normal",
                    "C_bloodPressure_abnormal",
                    "D_bloodGlucose_abnormal",
                    "D_bloodPressure_normal"
                ]
            },
            "study-results"
        ]
    }
}

